Brax.Me Privacy Policy
======================

**Your Privacy**  
  
We place extraordinary importance to your privacy and protecting it while you use our app. As part of our desire to provide security for your data, we also need to be confident of your identity so that your contacts and friends know to whom they are talking to.  
  
**What information do we collect?**  
  
During signup, we collect your name. It is not required that you give your real name, however it may be difficult for you to be identified by your friends if you don't provide some name they will recognize. You can always change this at any time.  
  
We optionally ask you to enter an email address. You must have access to this email address. We will verify it for your protection. The email address is primarily used for password recovery.  
  
You use a @username for people to use to contact you on the app without using any other identifier.  
  
We ask for an optional mobile phone to send you SMS (text) messages. This is solely used for password recovery.  
  
We do not store your password directly (we use something called an irreversible hash). This means that we cannot see your password or log in to your account without your knowledge. We are also unable to change your passwords for you.  
  
We do not extract or store EXIF data from your photos in My Photos other than to read the orientation of the photo. We then strip out the EXIF data upon storage. We do not read EXIF data of photo files in My Files. It is encrypted directly.  
  
We do not track anything in cookies. We do not track your location or your IP address. Your device retains an encrypted form of your login information for quick access to the app when you are logged in. This login information is removed when you log out.  
  
If you click on an external link posted by other users, other websites may create cookies that track you. Note that those links mean you have left this app.  
  
If we detect an attack on our servers (such as setting up multiple accounts, or denial of service attempts), we reserve the right to begin fingerprinting you to lock access to the app.  
  
**We Do Not Share your Info**  
  
We do not sell, exchange, or transfer your email address, or SMS number to other companies without your express permission. We will contact you via email only in relation to this app (such as messages and alerts).  
  
We do not collect personally identifiable information (PII). There are no "profiles" on you. You are free to reveal information to those you are communicating with on your own. We do not provide information on your actions to any outside party or track you for the purpose of advertising.  
  
**Confidentiality of Your Data**  
  
We take extraordinary precautions to ensure that your data remains private. Even with a security breach, your data is resistant to hacking both from external or internal players.  
  
When you send messages and create posts, be assured that your content is kept in non-human readable form. It is also designed to be unreadable to us. Your private data is always encrypted whether in storage or in transit. Note that there are public areas in Brax.Me and those are readable and open, although the identity of the posters can be aliased or anonymous. Open Membership areas are clearly labeled.  
  
**HIPAA Compliant (USA)**  
  
Except for Open Membership Rooms, all features of this app are HIPAA compliant (ensuring privacy of Medical information). Because our company is not able to see your private content, there is no necessity for a Business Associate Agreement but we will sign the agreement if asked to do so. This app is safe for use in provider-to-provider and provider-patient communications.  
  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
  
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into account and going to the 'Profile' page.  
  
**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our app, website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
  
**Your Consent**  
  
By using our Mobile App and site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  
  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website at https://brax.me.  
  
**Contacting Us**  
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
  
Brax.Me  
13428 Maxella Ave #560  
Marina Del Rey, CA 90292
